Now, that we've made some conclusions,
我们已经得出了一些结论
we can create visualizations to display our findings regarding
现在可以来创建可视化界面 展示我们的发现了
the associations between wine quality and different properties of wine.
即葡萄酒质量与不同葡萄酒性质之间的关系
I've already imported pandas and loaded our edited wine quality data.
我已经导入了 Pandas 并加载了我们处理好的葡萄酒质量数据
Let's also include the matplotlib inline statement to view plots in our notebook.
使用 % matplotlib inline 语句 在 Notebook 里查看图形
Let's create visualizations, to help us understand if a certain type of wine,
我们来创建可视化界面 这能帮我们理解葡萄酒的类型
red or white, is associated with higher quality.
也就是红葡萄酒还是白葡萄酒 是否与质量高低有关
In the previous section,
上一节中
we used groupby to find the mean wine quality for each color.
我们使用 groupby 语句找出了每种颜色的葡萄酒质量平均值
We're going to use these results for these visualizations.
现在我们要用这个结果来创建可视化界面
To do this, we can add plot to the end of the groupby statement.
要实现该操作 我们需要在 groupby 语句后面加上 plot
We can also specify parameters for the title,
也可以用参数说明柱形图的标题、
as well as the color and transparency of the bars.
颜色和透明度
Let's actually create a separate list for colors to make this cleaner.
我们重起一行写明颜色参数吧 这样看起来更清楚些
This makes sense, when there are multiple colors you want to graph with multiple times.
如果你绘制的图形有多种颜色 你又需要多次绘图 这么做能让代码更简洁明了
For our final visualizations,
最后一个可视化操作
we should have appropriate labels for both the x and y axis.
我们得给 x 和 y 轴创建合适的标签
We also don't want our white bar disappearing into a white background.
我们不想让白色的柱形和白色的背景融合起来
At this point, we can't get away with using only pandas.
但只用 pandas 是无计可施的
Let's add matplotlib. Pyplot is a module in matplotlib we'll use to create our plots.
让我们导入 matplotlib pyplot 是 matplotlib 的一个模块 可用于绘制图表
Standard convention is to import it and alias it as plt.
标准做法是把它导入进来 并赋予别名 plt
Let's also import seaborn.
再导入 seaborn
Seaborn standard alias is sns.
seaborn 的标准别名为 sns
Even if we don't use seaborn directly,
哪怕我们不直接使用 seaborn
it adds additional formatting to our plots that make them more
它也能够为我们的图表增加额外的样式
aesthetically pleasing, than standard matplotlib.
比起标准 matplotlib seaborn 能让图形更赏心悦目
Additional information on this is provided below.
更多有关 seaborn 的信息请查看下方
Now, that we have matplotlib, we can set x and y axis labels like this.
现在我们有了 matplotlib 我们可以像这样设定 x 和 y 轴的标签了
Our graph looks nicer and the white part doesn't blend into the background.
现在我们的图形更好看了 白色的部分也不会融合到背景中了
Although this works, that first line of code is pretty long and difficult to read.
这么做虽然奏效 但第一行代码特别长 很难读
Let's assign the groupby statement to a new object.
所以我们要把 groupby 语句分配给一个新对象
This won't change the visualization itself,
这样既不会改变可视化界面本身
It just makes our lives easier.
又能让我们更方便地工作